[Music]
I'm GNA try this uh do I do what make
Kool-Aid uh no I I don't make Kool-Aid
you don't ask a black woman if she make
Kool-Aid for
Thanksgiving for two reasons by the way
one because uh it's racist and
two because of course she
[Applause]
did oh God that's so Primal oh it's
horrible oh it's like two lions fighting
over a zebra caucus or something right
except in this case the zebra caucus is
a is a 50in wraparound HDTV from Vio
they make great stuff Larry when I was
in fourth grade absolutely I picked a
wedgie in front of the entire School
fourth grade little fourth grade grce
picking a wedgie in front of the entire
school you know what the kids called me
Wedgie Woman cuz that's what I was not a
protester of comfortable underwear
absolutely if somebody accuses me of
making fun of blind people my excuse
can't be look you know my my neck
started hurting so I just started moving
it like this you know and and then you
know it just it just it it got kind of
bright in there so I put some shades on
and just moving my neck then my voice I
just started doing it I God
Dam oh come on y'all I said hey
references to the slave trade would be
changed to the Atlantic triangular
trade come on you guys remember the
Atlantic triangular trade right don't
you right that's when americ trapped a
surplus of
triangles and the triangles help build
this nation and in turn receive separate
but equilateral treatment come on it's
like the personification of like uh of
Internet comments it's like think sucks
I'm the
best
true finally comments is running for
president comments
cover up cover up cover up cover up
cover up cover up cover up cover up some
sort of cover up cover up cover up fos
for as in everybody involved in this
cover up
is so this is based on a 2600 year old
play list EST Strada right written by
Aristophanes Aristophanes right he loves
satire satz greased at that time and we
felt that this the premise which is
women going on a sex strike to stop
right the war Ian so the women refuse to
have sex with the men right to have to
get peace right and then the men get
frustrated yes so I'm assuming these
aren't married
men we're just not as advanced as we
think we are sadly on Race I mean it it
it's we don't even have Band-Aids for
black people look what's going on here
white people bandaid mean I got to wear
white people bandaids that's
crazy where's where's El sharp on this I
don't want to come to any Hasty
conclusion iions at this point is it a
literal War on Christmas this is why the
media always drives me nuts instead of
reporting the news they just love to
guess you know they they get into this
game of of speculation and conjecture or
as I like to call it premature con
jaculation Santa not everybody wants
guns but you know these are kind of the
times we live in oh don't tell me about
the times I keep up with the times heck
I call Donna Joyce now because she
identifies as a woman like I you know I
I I'm cool I'm cool with whateves white
sounding names I don't know what that
means you are more likely to get hired
that's up yeah is that true you
think I don't know Larry yeah Larry I
got a job oh my
God Robin Larry and Robin I know hey
America follow the nightly show with
Larry Wilmore on Twitter but don't
follow me home I want followers but I
don't want followers that's stalking